[
  {
    "question": "How many gameticks do mobs spawned in portals exist for before they are teleported to the opposite dimension?",
    "choices": [
      "2 gt",
      "4 gt",
      "6 gt",
      "8 gt"
    ],
    "answer": "2 gt"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many items per hour can a hopper transport?",
    "choices": [
      "2,000",
      "5,000",
      "9,000",
      "15,000"
    ],
    "answer": "9,000"
  },
  {
    "question": "How often can villagers summon an iron golem?",
    "choices": [
      "700 gt",
      "100 gt",
      "1,000 gt",
      "500 gt"
    ],
    "answer": "700 gt"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many items can you fit in a shulker box?",
    "choices": [
      "1,728",
      "65,536",
      "4,096",
      "3,456"
    ],
    "answer": "1,728"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many time(s) can minecarts snap to rails vertically in one gametick?",
    "choices": [
      "1 time",
      "2 times",
      "3 times",
      "4 times"
    ],
    "answer": "2 times"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Evan Anâ€™s Minecraft Username?",
    "choices": [
      "zaqxswcdevfr",
      "Leaf_Ask",
      "EvanAn",
      "EvenAnd"
    ],
    "answer": "Leaf_Ask"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the radius of the despawn sphere?",
    "choices": [
      "24 blocks",
      "128 blocks",
      "64 blocks",
      "32 blocks"
    ],
    "answer": "128 blocks"
  },
  {
    "question": "How long is the item despawn timer?",
    "choices": [
      "10 minutes",
      "15 minutes",
      "5 minutes",
      "1 minute"
    ],
    "answer": "5 minutes"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many gameticks is equal to one redstone tick?",
    "choices": [
      "4 gt",
      "10 gt",
      "6 gt",
      "2 gt"
    ],
    "answer": "2 gt"
  },
  {
    "question": "What block behaves similar to pistons?",
    "choices": [
      "Redstone Lamp",
      "Iron Door",
      "Redstone Repeater",
      "Observer"
    ],
    "answer": "Iron Door"
  }
]